[{"question": "Who won Wimbledon in 2008?",
"answers": ["Rafa Nadal", "Rafael Nadal"]},
{"question": "Who wrote 'The last days of Socrates'?",
"answers": ["Plato"]},
{"question": "Who was the world's first billionaire?",
"answers": ["John D. Rockafeller"]},
{"question": "Who beat Carl Lewis in the 1988 Olympic hundred meters?",
"answers": ["Ben Johnson"]},
{"question": "Who penned the Hobbit?",
"answers": ["Tolkien", "J. R. R. Tolkien",
"John Ronald Rheul Tolkien"]},
{"question": "Who founded Google?", 
"answers": ["Larry Page", "Sergey Brin", "Page and Brin", "Brin and Page",
	   "Larry Page and Sergey Brin", "Sergey Brin and Larry Page"]},
{"question": "Who ran the first four-minute mile?",
"answers": ["Roger Bannister"]},
{"question": "Who won the tennis grand slam in 1962?",
"answers": ["Rod Laver"]},
{"question": "Who invented the C programming language?",
"answers": ["Dennis Ritchie"]},
{"question": "Who invented Lisp?",
"answers": ["John McCarthy"]},
{"question": "Who is the fastest runner in the world?",
"answers": ["Usain Bolt"]},
{"question": "Who was the first man on the moon?",
"answers": ["Neil Armstrong"]},
{"question": "Who was the command module pilot on the Apollo 11 moon mission?",
"answers": ["Michael Collins"]},
{"question": "Who directed the 1997 movie Titanic?",
"answers": ["James Cameron", "Jim Cameron"]},
{"question": "Who wrote the James Bond novels?",
"answers": ["Ian Fleming", "Ian Lancaster Fleming"]}
]